<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdmo xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" created="2025-08-12T18:27:05.704153+02:00" required="2.1.0" version="2.3.2">
	<view dc:uri="https://rdmo-hackathon-25.de/terms/views/rdmo-readme">
		<uri_prefix>https://rdmo-hackathon-25.de/terms</uri_prefix>
		<uri_path>rdmo-readme</uri_path>
		<dc:comment/>
		<order>0</order>
		<title lang="en">ReadMe</title>
		<help lang="en">This view provides an initial draft for a README that can be used when publishing data.</help>
		<title lang="de">ReadMe</title>
		<help lang="de">Diese Ansicht bietet einen ersten Entwurf für ein ReadMe, das bei einer Datenpublikation genutzt werden kann.</help>
		<title lang="es">ReadMe</title>
		<help lang="es">Esta vista proporciona un primer borrador de un Léame que puede utilizarse para la publicación de datos.</help>
		<title lang="fr">ReadMe</title>
		<help lang="fr">Cette vue fournit une première ébauche d'un ReadMe qui peut être utilisé lors d'une publication de données.</help>
		<title lang="it">ReadMe</title>
		<help lang="it">Questa vista fornisce una prima bozza di ReadMe che può essere utilizzata per la pubblicazione dei dati.</help>
		<catalogs>
			<catalog dc:uri="https://rdmorganiser.github.io/terms/questions/rdmo"/>
		</catalogs>
		<template>{% load view_tags %}
{% load i18n %}

&lt;!-- THIS VIEW ONLY WORKS WITH RDMO EXPORT PLUGIN (https://github.com/MPDL/rdmo-plugins-readme) --&gt;
{% load rdmo_readme_tags %}

{% get_set 'project/dataset/id' as datasets %}
{% get_current_language as LANGUAGE_CODE %}

&lt;h1&gt;ReadMe&lt;/h1&gt;
    {%   if LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;de&quot; %}Dieses ReadMe enthält essentielle Informationen zum Verständnis dieses Datensatzes, um Transparenz, Nachvollziehbarkeit und Wiederverwendbarkeit der Daten sicherzustellen.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;es&quot; %}Este Léame contiene información esencial para comprender este conjunto de datos y garantizar su transparencia, trazabilidad y reutilización.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;fr&quot; %}Ce ReadMe contient des informations essentielles à la compréhension de cet ensemble de données, afin de garantir la transparence, la traçabilité et la réutilisation des données.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;it&quot; %}Questo ReadMe contiene informazioni essenziali per la comprensione di questa raccolta di dati per garantire la trasparenza, la tracciabilità e la riutilizzabilità dei dati.
    {% else %}This ReadMe contains essential information for understanding this dataset to ensure transparency, traceability and reusability of the data.
    {% endif %}&lt;!-- DISPLAY ENGLISH TEXT FOR ANY OTHER LANGUAGE_CODE --&gt;

{% if not datasets %}&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
    {%   if LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;de&quot; %}Bitte lege zuerst einen Datenmanagementplan an.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;es&quot; %}Por favor, cree primero un plan de gestión de datos.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;fr&quot; %}Veuillez d'abord créer un plan de gestion des données.
    {% elif LANGUAGE_CODE == &quot;it&quot; %}Creare prima un piano di gestione dei dati.
    {% else %}Please put some information in your data management plan.
    {% endif %}&lt;!-- DISPLAY ENGLISH TEXT FOR ANY OTHER LANGUAGE_CODE --&gt;

{% elif dataset == None %}&lt;br/&gt;
    {% for dataset in datasets %}    
        &lt;h2&gt;{{ dataset.value }}&lt;/h2&gt;
        {% render_dataset_block dataset LANGUAGE_CODE %}
    {% endfor %}

{% else %}
    &lt;!-- EXPORT PLUGIN: dataset parameter is passed to view --&gt;    
    {% render_dataset_block dataset LANGUAGE_CODE %}

{% endif %}</template>
	</view>
</rdmo>
